usage: uber-apk-signer -a <file/folder> | -h | -v [--allowResign] [--debug] [--dryRun]  [--ks <keystore>]
       [--ksAlias <alias>] [--ksDebug <keystore>] [--ksKeyPass <password>] [--ksPass <password>] [-l <path>]
       [-o <path>] [--overwrite] [--skipZipAlign]  [--verbose] [--verifySha256 <cert-sha256>] [-y]
       [--zipAlignPath <path>]
Version: 1.3.0
    -a,--apks <file/folder>           Can be a single apk or a folder containing multiple apks. These are used
                                      as source for zipalining/signing/verifying. It is also possible to
                                      provide multiple locations space seperated (can be mixed file folder):
                                      '/apk /apks2 my.apk'. Folder will be checked non-recursively.
       --allowResign                  If this flag is set, the tool will not show error on signed apks, but
                                      will sign them with the new certificate (therefore removing the old
                                      one).
       --debug                        Prints additional info for debugging.
       --dryRun                       Check what apks would be processed without actually doing anything.
    -h,--help                         Prints help docs.
       --ks <keystore>                The keystore file. If this isn't provided, will tryto sign with a debug
                                      keystore. The debug keystore will be searched in the same dir as
                                      execution and 'user_home/.android' folder. If it is not found there a
                                      built-in keystore will be used for convenience. It is possible to pass
                                      one or multiple keystores. The syntax for multiple params is
                                      '<index>=<keystore>' for example: '1=keystore.jks'. Must match the
                                      parameters of --ksAlias.
       --ksAlias <alias>              The alias of the used key in the keystore. Must be provided if --ks is
                                      provided. It is possible to pass one or multiple aliases for multiple
                                      keystore configs. The syntax for multiple params is '<index>=<alias>'
                                      for example: '1=my-alias'. Must match the parameters of --ks.
       --ksDebug <keystore>           Same as --ks parameter but with a debug keystore. With this option the
                                      default keystore alias and passwords are used and any arguments relating
                                      to these parameter are ignored.
       --ksKeyPass <password>         The password for the key. If this is not provided, caller will get a
                                      user prompt to enter it. It is possible to pass one or multiple
                                      passwords for multiple keystore configs. The syntax for multiple params
                                      is '<index>=<password>'. Must match the parameters of --ks.
       --ksPass <password>            The password for the keystore. If this is not provided, caller will get
                                      a user prompt to enter it. It is possible to pass one or multiple
                                      passwords for multiple keystore configs. The syntax for multiple params
                                      is '<index>=<password>'. Must match the parameters of --ks.
    -l,--lineage <path>               The lineage file for apk signer schema v3 if more then 1 signature is
                                      used. See here https://bit.ly/2mh6iAC for more info.
    -o,--out <path>                   Where the aligned/signed apks will be copied to. Must be a folder. Will
                                      create, if it does not exist.
       --overwrite                    Will overwrite/delete the apks in-place
       --skipZipAlign                 Skips zipAlign process. Also affects verify.
    -v,--version                      Prints current version.
       --verbose                      Prints more output, especially useful for sign verify.
       --verifySha256 <cert-sha256>   Provide one or multiple sha256 in string hex representation (ignoring
                                      case) to let the tool check it against hashes of the APK's certificate
                                      and use it in the verify process. All given hashes must be present in
                                      the signature to verify e.g. if 2 hashes are given the apk must have 2
                                      signatures with exact these hashes (providing only one hash, even if it
                                      matches one cert, will fail).
    -y,--onlyVerify                   If this is passed, the signature and alignment is only verified.
       --zipAlignPath <path>          Pass your own zipalign executable. If this is omitted the built-in
                                      version is used (available for win, mac and linux)
